Inventory of the John Ehrlichman Papers, 1963-1982
Hoover Institution Archives
- NIXON ADMINISTRATION FILE, Appendix A - Documents: Files (Box 1-3)
  - RN view of DOJ (TT/Sneed/E), Ivy League-those frilly games (Aspen), Keep some incompetent blacks, Wash. elite-most hated TT, Burger, Rhenquist, E's leftwingers, Kleindienst creature of DO J, Sneed-Texan-born pol, Recruiting for DO J, Sally Ann Payto 'on crt track' -, (8 pages), 12/8/72 10a
  - Brenniger not a Catholic (TT/H/E), wasting Krogh, Poor Cabinet, image, PP, Fresh Ideas, Criteria for Cabinet, Anne Armstrong, Georgetown influences-Disraeli & Aristocracy, New N constituency-not suburbia, Only Brennan & I come from working class, Borko & Buchanens survive & become "great nuts", Reagan, Movie for secys, Black women for S/ct, W/G & Chapin, JNM failed, Dean Report-before Xmas-during for. peace action, Chapin leaving, Strachan-H defends, Statement soon-no one in WH but DC & Strachan, (8 pages), 12/11/72
  - Tax/E pol/not Sh, RK note via RMW re/Gray (TT/H/E), Ann Armstrong-Tokenism, Brenniger-mistake, Tokens, Pottinger, (4 pages), 12/13/72
  - Director for FBI, Gray pro & con (TT Kleindenst E), Matt Byrne, Felt the leak, Martha-"sick"-JNM could have prevented W/G, Hoover-no controversy, -died just in time, -the breakfast-strikeout, Football/blackout T.V., (5 pages), 12/18/72
  - Restaff, secret service chgs. (TT/H/E), (4 pages), 12/18/72
  - Diary: 2/-4/, (6 pages), 1973
  - Newbould Noye's letter to the TT, (Missing pages), 1/17/73
  - during confirmation (Pat Gray), Gray talks w/me re:, W/G, (3 pages), 3/8/73 phone
  - Brennan, CC running DOL (Sh ph), Appointees, (2 pages), 2/12/73
  - Pat Hill (TT Ph), Belzano, (2 pages), 2/19/73
  - J.B. Connally, El Paso Gas case (C ph), W/G, (6 pages), 3/28/73
  - Sam Ervin, phone conv. re committee leaks, secret mtgs., (Missing pages), 4/2/73
  - GRAY nomination w/drawn, innocent victim, broken man but not a POW for 7 years. It's all relative, (1 page), 4/6/73
  - Civil settlements, Ervin Leak (J.N. Mitchell phone), (3 pages), 4/11/73
  - W./G. Report to TT by E (JE), (8 pages), 4/17/73
  - Tape/nb - TT & Dk Moore, (7 pages), 4/19/73
  - Rules 2nd Mting (Howard Baker phone), Ervin attacks on TT, (Missing Contents pages), 4/13/73
  - re: committee's procedural rules (Ervin/Baker phone), (7 pages), 4/16/73
  - Hunt & Liddy (Memo-Silbert to H. Petersen), broke in Ellsbergs psych., (1 page), 4/16/73
  - Macgruder-press (C. Colson phone), (5 pages), 4/20/73
  - Colson-W/G, notes of mtg. w/CC, (3 pages), 4/23/73
  - Ziegler delivers the message:, H & E must go (Ziegler), Dispute re what JBC says (H & E), (6 pages), 4/25/73
  - What JBC said, LEAVE OF ABSENCE (TT/H/E), JNM MAY LIE ABOUT E, ROGERS, H LISTEN TO TAPES OF TT/DEAN, Fire Dean-no immunity, Clemency, H Peterson-coddling Dean-wait, Leave for all, (12 pages), 4/25/73
  - Kleindienst resign, Richardson (Phone-Ziegler), Dean, Mitchell 4/15 or 4/16, Colson 4/16 - Dean, (8 pages), 4/30/73
  - re Ellsberg break in -, Did I know sooner? (TT/E), E-nod, TT: If so, I don't recall, (3 pages), 5/2/73
  - Reports, statements, charts, military cables, memoranda and letters relating to General William Westmoreland, CBS, and enemy force estimates during the Vietnam war, 1963-1982
- AUDIOVISUAL FILE, Appendix B - John Ehrlichman Media Tapes Dating from 1/30/71 to 7/30/78 (Box 4-17)
  Audiotapes relating to Watergate, primarily recordings of news broadcasts. Arranged chronologically; see Appendix B for detailed box list (prepared by the Archives of Artists of New Mexico and the Southwest).
  - "Impeachment", Mike Wallace/John Lofton/, Helen Thomas/Anthony Lewis/, Daniel Ellsberg:, 2 Sides, Undated (Box 4, Tape 1)
  - Judge John J. Sirica, TV Capsules, Undated (Tape 2)
  - Les Whitten, JE-DE NEW (?!), Undated (Tape 3)
  - Side 1: Hunt/Dean Segs., Side 2: Sen. Frank Church on CIA, Undated (Tape 4)
  - The Cooney's and Guests, WMCA Radio (Talk Show) on RN/Ford/Impeachment/etc., 2 Sides, Undated (Tape 5)
  - John Ehrlichman, CBS Radio - Washington Week, 1/30/71 (Tape 6)
  - J. E., On CBS Television, 4/29/71 (Tape 7)
  - J. E., Watergate Hearings, Part Two/ABC and NET, 7/24/73 (Tape 8)
  - J. E., Television, CBS TV/NBC TV/ABC, Hearings: Start: NBC TV/NET TV, Side 2: J. E., CBS TV Special (hour) 10 p.m., 7/24/73 (Tape 9)
  - J. E., "Hearings" NET/NBC TV - Comments: 2 p.m. start/recess, Side 2: J. E., "Hearings" Recess and End, Comments: NET/NBC TV, 7/24/73 (Tape 10)
  - J. E. (Box 1), Side 1: Watergate Hearings (Noon), Track 1: WNET, Track 3: CBS, Side 2: Track 1: NET TV, Track 3: CBS TV, 7/24/73 (Tape 11)
  - J. E. (Box 2), Watergate Hearings, Track 1: NET, Track 3: Network, 2 Sides, 7/24-25/73 (Tape 12)
  - J. E. (Box 3), "Hearings" (Final part), Side 2: CBS TV Special 10 p.m., TV News Capsules added, 7/25/73-7/26/73 (Tape 13)
  - J. E., "Hearings" Side 1: 2 p.m. start/recess, Side 2: NET/CBS TV Comments, "Recess" Ervin Interview/Aide Interview, 7/25/73 (Tape 14)
  - J. E., Watergate Hearings, Track 1: NET/Track 3: NET, 2 Sides, 7/25/73 (Tape 15)
  - J. E., "Hearings" NET/CBS TV Comments:, Start/Noon......, Side 2: Attorney Wilson Comments, 7/25/73 (Tape 16)
  - J. E., Watergate Hearings (Part 2), 2 p.m. session, 2 Sides, 7/26/73 (Box 5, Tape 17)
  - J. E., "Hearings" 2 Sides - ABC/NET, 7/26/73 (Tape 18)
  - J. E., "Hearings" 2 Sides, Track 1 - NET, Track 3 - ABC, 7/26/73 (Tape 19)
  - J. E., Watergate Hearings, NET/ABC TV Comments, Start/Noon/Recess/End, 2 Sides, 7/26/73 (Tape 20)
  - J. E., Watergate Hearings, 2 Sides, 7/27/73 (Tape 21)
  - J. E., Watergate Hearings, 2 Sides, 7/27/73 (Tape 22)
  - J. E., Watergate Hearings, 2 Sides, 7/27/73 (Tape 23)
  - J. E., "Hearings" Comments: NET/NBC TV, 2 Sides (Parts 1 and 2), 7/27/73 (Tape 24)
  - J. E., Watergate Hearings, 2 Sides, 7/27/73 (Tape 25)
  - J. E., TV News Capsules, Side 2: "Washington Week Review", NET TV, RN/JE/Cambodia/etc., 7/27/73-7/28/73 (Tape 26)
  - J. E., "Hearings" (Part 3) Comments by NET/NBC TV, Side 2: Author FBI Agent, Connors on RN/JE/etc., NBC Radio 8 to 9 p.m., 7/27/73 (Tape 27)
  - "Watergate" CBS TV Special 8 p.m., NBC TV Special 9 p.m., 2 Sides, 7/27/73 (Tape 28)
  - TV capsules, 2 sides, 7/27-30/73 (Tape 29)
  - J. E., "Hearings" NET/CBS TV Start/Noon/End, JE Interview, 2 Sides, (Network TV News Comments on JE at end of Side 2), 7/30/73 (Tape 30)
  - J. E., Watergate Hearings, Part One: NET and Network, Track 1: NET/Track 3: Network, 2 Sides, 7/30/73 (Tape 31)
  - J. E., Watergate Hearings, Part 3/NET and Network, Side 2: H. R. H., 7/30/73 (Tape 32)
  - J. E./H. R. H., Watergate Hearings, NOTE: Final part of HRH is midway on Side 2, Track 3/after Network discussion, 7/30/73 (Box 6, Tape 33)
  - "The Advocates" "Should the President Be Impeached", NET TV, 2 Sides, 12/9/73 (Tape 34)
  - Side 1: Lowell Weicker, ABC TV, Side 2: TV News Capsules on RN - Taxes, 12/9/73 (Tape 35)
  - WPIX TV on Juror/Debate, 10 p.m., 1/2/74 (Tape 36)
  - Side 1: G. Gordon Liddy, "60 Minutes" Side 2: NBC TV Report '74-75, 1/5/74 (Tape 37)
  - TV capsules, 2 sides, 1/11-15/74 (Tape 38)
  - Egil Korgh, "60 Minutes "and other TV News from 1/24-25/74, 2 Sides, 1/27/74 (Tape 39)
  - Side 1: TV capsules, 1/29/74-1/28/74 (Tape 40)
  - Grand Jury Indictments, TV News Capsules/Specials, 2 Sides, 3/1/74 (Tape 41)
  - TV Capsules, RN/Vesco/JM/Chapin/etc., Wilbur Mills Interview, 2 Sides, 3/1/74 (Tape 42)
  - Side 1: TV Capsules, 3/2/74, Side 2: TV Capsules, 3/3/74, 3/2/74-3/3/74 (Tape 43)
  - TV Capsules, 2 Sides, 3/4/74 (Tape 44)
  - TV Sound Capsules - Side 1, 3/5/74 TV Sound Capsules - Side 2, 3/6/74 (Tape 45)
  - President Richard M. Nixon's Press Conference, Comments on Side 2, 3/6/74 (Tape 46)
  - Side 1: Radio WMCA Bob Grant talks with Anthony Lewis of New York Times, CBS TV a.m. Panel Discussion, Metromedia/WPIX RV, Side 2: TV Capsules, CBS TV/ABC TV/NBC TV Networks, a.m. TV: Douglas - Voorhees/Govs, 3/7/74 (Tape 47)
  - Side 1: "Washington Week Review", 3/8/74 NET TV, Side 2: TV Capsules, "60 Minutes" Kilpatrick - von Hoffman on RN Aides, 3/9/74 (Tape 48)
  - J. E., TV: 3/11, 2 Sides, 3/11/74 (Box 7, Tape 49)
  - J. E., TV Capsules, 2 Sides, 3/12-13/74 (Tape 50)
  - Side 1: Vice President Ford, CBS TV a.m. Interview on RN and News spots, Side 2: Networks:, Ford/Julie/Cubans/JM/Woods: CBS, Ford - HK/Mills/Shultz/RN/Cubans/JM/JC: ABC, Bebe/Woods/Cubans/RN/House/JM/Pat: NBC, 3/14/74 (Tape 51)
  - Side 1: Schoumacher AB Radio, Side 2: WMCA Phones/RN at '01 Opry', 3/17/74 (Tape 52)
  - Sirica/JM/RN/Buchanan, TV Capsules, 2 Sides, 3/18/74 (Tape 53)
  - President Richard M. Nixon, NAB Press Conference, Houston, Texas, Side 2: Comments, 3/19/74 (Tape 54)
  - Side 1: TV networks, Side 2: Buckley statement/and a.m. TV, 3/19/74 (Tape 55)
  - TV Capsules, Side 1: Roy Cohn on NET for RN and news capsules added, Side 2: RN/House/JE/JM/Bebe/etc., 3/20-21/74 (Tape 56)
  - Side 1: Howard Baker "Issues", 3/24/74, "Washington Week in Review "NET, 3/22/74, TV News Capsules, 3/22/74, Side 2: TV News Capsules, Conyers/Wilson/Appeal/Albert/Bebe/, ABA Smith Interview/Halpern Tap/RN/, GSA/CBS Radio "Washington Week"/etc., 3/22-24/74 (Tape 57)
  - 2 Sides: Carl Albert NET TV, Side 2: Interview, 3/25/74 (Tape 58)
  - TV Capsules March 26, '74, Grand Jury Report/JM-Dean/, Court/oil-CBS/ABC/and NBC TV, 2 Sides, 3/26/74 (Tape 59)
  - Side 1: NET TV "Behind the Lines", The Media and the Presidency, Side 2: TV Capsules, 3/28/74 (Tape 60)
  - Side 1: TV, 3/30/74; CBS: (Rather) Ford/GOP/Percy/HK, RN - Taxes/Schorr on IRS Mail - RN/, JE/RN - Welfare/Zumwatt/Migrants/P, Energy/Dems, NBC: HK Weds/HK/Ford/RN - Taxes/, Butz/Beef/RN - Hearst, ABC: Reasoner Report: "Arabs", Radio: RN - Taxes/JE/Percy/JE/Taxes/, Dems/HK/Dems/Ford/Dayan/Sadat/HK/, Ford/Taxes/Ford/JE/Jessup/HK/HK, Side 2: "Washington Week Review", NET TV: Discussing HK/RN - Jaworski/, 3/29/74; Congress/HHH/Milk, HHH Interview "Today"/a.m. TV News, TV News segments on Networks for March 29th, '74, 7 p.m. (Tape 61)
  - Side 1: Wilbur Mills "Issues""World This Week "CBS, 4/7/74; Side 2: "Washington Week in Review "NET, 4/5/74 (Tape 62)
  - Side 1: "Merv "TV, Frank Mankiewicz/Herb Klein/Father, McLaughlin Guests on RN, Side 2: IRS Alexander on Meet Press, Rep. John Rhodes on "Face Nation", Nobelsville on RB/von H-Kilpatrick/Bebe, 4/6/74 (Tape 63)
  - Side 1: TV Capsules, 4/9/74; Side 2: Lowell Weicker Testimony and News Capsules/JE, 4/8/74 (Tape 64)
  - TV Capsules, 2 Sides, 4/10/74 (Box 8, Tape 65)
  - Side 1: TV capsules, Side 2: Helen Thomas/McClendon, 4/15/74 (Tape 66)
  - J. E., Side 1: TV Capsules: 4/17, Side 2: TV Capsules: 4/16, 4/16/74-4/17/74 (Tape 67)
  - TV capsules, 2 sides, 4/22/74 (Tape 68)
  - TV Sound Capsules, 2 Sides, 4/23-24/74 (Tape 69)
  - Side 1: President Richard M. Nixon talk Comments: CBS TV/ABC TV/NBC TV CBS Radio Rangel/Julie, 4/29/74; Side 2: Comments: NET TV-Rewhitt-Hess/ Railsback; WBAI FM/WINS Radio/ Schoenbrun comment (Tape 70)
  - "The Day After the President's Talk on the Transcripts" 2 sides, 4/30/74 (Tape 71)
  - Presidential Transcript (2nd day after), 2 sides, 5/1/74 (Tape 72)
  - Transcripts.....News, 2 Sides, 5/2-3/74 (Tape 73)
  - Side 1: NET TV, 5/3/74; "Washington Week in Review" Nets: CBS: TV News, Side 2: CBS TV Continued:, ABC TV/NBC TV:, Carson "Raps "RN, Radio, 5/4/74 (Tape 74)
  - Side 1: "Oil "JE/ABC TV; "Face Nation "James St. Clair; "Issues "Alexander Haig; Steward Alsop "Bob Grant "Radio, Side 2: "Impeachment "WMCA Radio; JM-Stans trial report; Reps. Smith and Fish on RN, 5/5/74 (Tape 75)
  - Side 1 and 2: TV Capsules, 5/6/74-5/7/74 (Tape 76)
  - Tapes/Transcripts, Side 1: TV Capsules, Side 2: "Impeachment "NET TV, "Straight Talk "Sen. Ted Kennedy, 5/8/74 (Tape 77)
  - Side 1: Alger Hiss Interview NET TV, Side 2: CBS TV/ABC TV Commentaries on Judiciary Session #1 (Live), 5/8/74 (Tape 78)
  - Side 1: Jack Anderson/Carson, TV News: Metromedia/WPIX, Dr. McLaughlin - Bob Grant phone call, a.m. TV, Side 2: TV Capsules CBS/ABC, Judiciary Live NBC Session #1, 5/9/74 (Tape 79)
  - TV/Radio capsules, Transcripts/RN - Box #1, 5/10-11/74 (Tape 80)
  - Side 1: E. Howard Hunt/Buckley, Side 2: "Washington Week in Review "NET Box #2, 5/12/74 (Box 9, Tape 81)
  - RN/Transcripts, etc., TV Capsules: May 13th, 2 Sides, 5/13/74 (Tape 82)
  - TV capsules, RN/transcripts, 5/14/74 (Tape 83)
  - Side 1: TV Capsules (Nets), 5/15/74; RN/House/Tapes, 1974 RN/House/Tapes, 5/16/74; Side 2: a.m. TV, 5/17/74; Judiciary/RN/JE/Bebe/etc., a.m. TV RN/Tapes/House, 5/15/74; Robert Strauss "Straight Talk", NET TV (Tape 84)
  - RN/Transcripts, etc., TV Coverages, 2 Sides, 5/17/74 (Tape 85)
  - RN/House/Sirica/J, RN Radio Talk/Rodino Interview NET TV, 2 Sides, 5/20/74 (Tape 86)
  - TV capsules, RN/House, 5/21-22/74 (Tape 87)
  - Side 1: Korff-others "51st State "NET TV, WPIX: RN tapes/Doar; Metro: HK/Abend-Riesel on Mideast/RN; Doar/McL/RN/EK/McCord/McL/HK, Side 2: Ted Koppel on Barry Gray discuss HK Nets: CBS/NBC/ABC on RN-tapes/House, 5/23/74 (Tape 88)
  - Side 1: Sen. Byrd "Face", 5/26/74; ABC Smith "Meet Press", a.m. TV, 5/27/74; Side 2: Washington Week Review/NET TV, 5/24/74; a.m.: Duke/Rather/RN/Saxbe/RN/, Perspective on Ford/H/Duke/K-von H./, Burns/RN/Byrd/Poll/etc. (Tape 89)
  - TV capsules, Side 1: 5/27-28, Side 2: Barry Gray Radio, 5/28 (Tape 90)
  - Side 1: Riesel-Abend on K's-RN, 5/29/74; TV Capsules, Side 2: Greenspan/Snyder "Tomorrow "NBC and TV Capsules, 5/30/74 (Tape 91)
  - TV Capsules, 2 Sides, 5/31-6/2/74 (Tape 92)
  - TV Capsules, 2 Sides, 6/3/74 (Tape 93)
  - TV Capsules, 2 Sides, 6/4/74 (Tape 94)
  - TV Capsules, 6/5/74; Side 1, Side 2, 6/6/74 (Tape 95)
  - TV Capsules, Networks/Gesell/JE/RN House/etc., Side 2: "Washington Week Review", 2 Sides, 6/7/74 (Tape 96)
  - RN Departs on Mideast Tour, JE/Gesell/etc., 2 Sides, 6/10/74 (Box 10, Tape 97)
  - TV Sound Capsules, RN-Cairo/JE/HK/etc., 6/11-12/74 (Tape 98)
  - President in Egypt/and other news, Side 1: TV capsules, Side 2: Jeb Magruder with Dick Cavett, 6/13/74 (Tape 99)
  - Side 1: TV Capsules, RN-Mideast/House/JE/HK/etc., Side 2: "Washington Week Review", and a.m. TV, JE, etc., 6/14/74 (Tape 100)
  - TV Capsules, Woodward and Bernstein Interview, 2 Sides, 6/18-19/74 (Tape 101)
  - TV Capsules, 2 Sides, 6/21-23/74 (Tape 102)
  - Side 1: TV Capsules (Nets), RN-Brussels/HJ/HK/JE/Mideast;, Side 2: TV a.m. RN Brussels/House/etc., 6/26/74 (Tape 103)
  - Side 1: TV, RN Arrival in Moscow NBC/ABC Live, Mike Mansfield Interview;, Side 2: a.m. TV CBS etc.: RN/House, JE/etc., 6/27/74 (Tape 104)
  - J. E., 2 Sides, 6/25-28/74 (Tape 105)
  - Side 1: "Update "Watergate," "Washington Week in Review "NET TV, RN News Capsules, Side 2: John McLaughlin ABC TV, Marchetti/CIA "Today", TV News Capsules, 6/28/74 (Tape 106)
  - TV Capsules, Colson "Today "Interview added, 2 Sides, 6/30-7/3/74 (Tape 107)
  - Side 1: JE-TV, 7/3/74; a.m. and p.m., 7/4/74; Colson-"Today", 7/5/74; Side 2: Colson (Part Two), 7/5/74; "Washington Week Review "NET (Tape 108)
  - TV Capsules, JE/RN/Colson Interviews, 2 Sides, 7/8-9/74 (Tape 109)
  - Side 1: TV Capsules, 7/10/74; Side 2: TV Composite, 7/11/74 etc. (Tape 110)
  - TV Capsules, 2 Sides, 7/12/74 (Tape 111)
  - Side 1: TV, 7/13/74; CBS: Watergate Report/JE/RN Ford, NBC: RN/Watergate Report/, "Washington Week "CBS Radio, Side 2: Face the Nation, Lowell Weicker - Guest, CBS TV, 7/14/74 (Tape 112)
  - "Sunday "NBC TV, Woodward-Bernstein, 2 Sides, 7/14/74 (Box 11, Tape 113)
  - Woodward and Bernstein with William F. Buckley, 2 Sides, 7/14/74 (Tape 114)
  - Side 1: JE, Side 2: "Tomorrow "Jarrell/Brocaw, Interviews on RN, 7/15-16/74 (Tape 115)
  - TV Capsules, RN/JE/St. Clair/Tape/etc., 7/18/74 (Tape 116)
  - Side 1: Ken Clawson "Tomorrow", 7/18/74; CBS TV Special "Impeachment", 7/18/74; Side 2: NET TV Special/Panel, 7/18/74; Korff "Today "and CBS TV a.m., 7/18/74 (Tape 117)
  - Side 1: Track, 7/19/74; TV: CBS: Doar/RN/Cyprus:, ABC and NBC also., Side 2: "Washington Week Review", TV, 7/20/74; CBS: House/C/Doar/Z/Tapes, NBC: C/Doar/Tapes-RN/Ford/etc. (Tape 118)
  - Side 1: James McCord "Tomorrow "NBC TV, Side 2: TV News: Hogan-Burch/etc., 7/23/74 (Tape 119)
  - TV Capsules, Court Decision/St. Clair Statement, House/Comments 3 Nets at 7 p.m.:, and a.m. TV, 2 Sides, 7/24/74 (Tape 120)
  - Side 1: TV; Theodore White/Latta interviews: News: NBC: House/ St. Clair/House/Miller/RN/Pro RN/ Tower-Brooke interviews; CBS: House/Ford/Hart comment/House/, Side 2: Reports on court decision. a.m. TV RN/Galbraith interview/House: NET-CBS comments on House hearings; Maraziti and Latta live talks, 7/25/74 (Tape 121)
  - TV capsules: Court/House/Jaworski/Sirica/ Impeach RN/L.A. Talk/comments, 7/25/74 (Tape 122)
  - Side 1: TV, 7/26/74; CBS: House/Sirica/RN/Poll/, Sevareid on RN, NBC: House/Poll/Ford/Sirica, ABC: House/Ford/Sirica/Smith-RN:, House Hearings Comments, 7/27/74; Side 2: NET/ABC TV Comments on Saturday, House Hearings:, Live Vote on Article 1:, CBS TV: Cronkite/Sevareid/Mudd (Tape 123)
  - Side 1: Rep. Thornton-Butler, 7/28/74; On Face the Nation, "Meet Press "Chas. Black Prof. on Court-RN, Rep./Railsback Interview Today, 7/26/74; Charles Sandman Today, a.m. CBS TV: House/Baker/Court, Side 2: "Newsmaker "CBS TV, 7/28/74; Sen. Jacob Javits, "Issues "Sen. Robert Byrd, a.m. TV RN $/House, 7/26/74 (Tape 124)
  - TV Capsules, Networks/a.m. TV/ABA Smith Interview/etc., 2 Sides, 7/29/74 (Tape 125)
  - Side 1: TV Capsules, CBS: House/Rhodes/Tapes/etc., ABC: House/RN-Tapes/HP/Reasoner Says, NBC: House/RN-Tapes/Dems. Brinkley Says, Interviews: Byrd/Sandman/Wiggins, Side 2: House Windup/NBC/NET Comments, a.m. TV: McClery/House/Ford/RN/JC/Ford/, Hart on Impeachment, PUX: House/Tapes/House, Metromedia: House/Abend on RN (Tape 126)
  - TV Capsules, 2 Sides, 7/31/74 (Tape 127)
  - Side 2: JE/House/RN/Tapes/Koroff/, Ford/Goldwater/House Interviews/Vox Pop RN, Side 1: TV Capsules, CBS: House/RN/Morton/Butterfield/S/C, ABC: RN/JC/Inflation/Smith, NBC: House/RN/Poll/Arends/Ford/JC/$, a.m. TV: House/RN/Pat B./ Burger/JE/JC/HJ, Dole Interviews on "Today"/RN, CBS: House/Montoya/Ford/Tapes/Senate/Burger, Javits Interview: BG/Wallace/Hogan/House/, Fish Jr./Rhodes, 8/1/74 (Tape 128)
  - Side 1: TV Capsules, CBS: Dean/Tapes/RN/COL./C, NBC: Dean/Tapes/HHH/COL./Mideast, ABC: Dean/Tapes/RN/House/RN/Rhodes, COL/HHH/Railsback-Mezvinsky/R/, a.m. TV: House/Dean/RN/RN/Vox/, Russell Train Interview, CBS: Dean/House/Senate/RN, Side 2: "Washington Week in Review", Discuss: RN-House-Rhodes/Senate/Cyprus/Greece, a.m. TV: Detoledano-Braden on RN/$/Hart/RN/, Jordan/Dean/COL/Japan, ABX: RN/Metro: Dean/WPIX/Dean/RN/$/Meany/, Dean/Grant on RN/RN/HHH on RN, 8/2/74 (Box 12, Tape 129)
  - TV/Radio, CBS: Ford/House/RN, NBC: RN/Ford/MM/Hogan, "Washington Week "CBS Radio, Reasoner: Impeachment Politics, WMCA phones/McCourt/Grant on RN, 2 Sides, 8/3/74 (Tape 130)
  - TV Capsules, News on RN/von Hoffman-Kilpatrick, Washington Post-Bradlee, Grahm....World This Week/Rush on Kup's Show, 2 Sides, 8/4/74 (Tape 131)
  - a.m. TV, Pest/RN/Tapes/Allen Interview/Paris on RN, RN/Rhodes/RN/Ford/Hart-Kempton on RN tapes/, Rules/Tokyo-London/Sandman, 2 Sides, 8/5/74 (Tape 132)
  - RN Flash/Statement/Networks, Radio-TV-Interviews, 2 Sides, 8/5/74 (Tape 133)
  - TV capsules, 8/7/74 (Tape 134)
  - TV capsules, Side 1: Networks on RN, Side 2: President Nixon's talks, 8/8/74 (Tape 135)
  - Side 1: TV news: RN/Ford/comments, Side 2: CBS TV special RN-Ford; "Washington Week in Review "NET RN-Ford, 8/9/74 (Tape 136)
  - TV capsules: JE/RN/Ford, 2 sides, 8/12/74 (Tape 137)
  - Side 1: Ford's press conference, Side 2: TV news, 8/28/74 (Tape 138)
  - TV Capsules, Ford/RN/JE, 2 Sides, 9/10/74 (Tape 139)
  - JOHN EHRLICHMAN, ----Trial----, 2 Sides, 10/1-21/74 (Tape 140)
  - J. E., -----Trial-----, 2 Sides, 10/18-11/8/74 (Tape 141)
  - J. E., 2 Sides, 11/11-26/74 (Tape 142)
  - J. E., 2 Sides, 11/27-12/6/74 (Tape 143)
  - "Verdict" TV-Radio Capsules, 2 Sides, (Box #1), 12/1/74 (Tape 144)
  - J. E., -----Trial-----, 2 Sides, 12/9-27/74 (Box 13, Tape 145)
  - "Verdict" Side 1: JOHN EHRLICHMAN "Today", Interview, (Box #2), 1/1-2/75 (Tape 146)
  - "Verdict," "Washington Week Review "NET, Agronsky and Company NET, 2 Sides, 1/2-4/75 (Tape 147)
  - Judge John J. Sirica, TV Capsules: "Release", 1/8/75 (Tape 148)
  - "Sirica" TV, 1/9/75 (Tape 149)
  - Side 1: Sirica, 1/10-11/75; Side 2: Magruder "Face Nation", 1/12/75 (Tape 150)
  - Side 1: "Roundtable "CIA, Side 2: Dean/Magruder....., 1/15-16/75 (Tape 151)
  - Javits, 1/19/75; CIA/FBI, 1/20/75 (Tape 152)
  - Side 1: CIA/Agee "Tomorrow", 1/29/75; Jack Anderson/CIA, Side 2: Magruder's "Tomorrow", 1/28/75, etc. (Tape 153)
  - Side 1: Watergate Jury/Mike Douglas, CIA etc......, Roundtable "Jews in American Politics", Side 2: "CIA "Tomorrow NBC TV, 2/6/75 (Tape 154)
  - Charles Colson, TV Capsules, Ron Ziegler Interview, 2/7/75 (Tape 155)
  - Side 1: Jack Anderson/Gregory NET, Side 2: Magruder's/Mike Douglas, 2/11/75 (Tape 156)
  - Judge John J. Sirica, Watergate Sentencing, 2/21/75 (Tape 157)
  - JOHN EHRLICHMAN, TV Capsules, 2 Sides, 2/23-24/75 (Tape 158)
  - Side 1: Jaworski on RN "Kup's", 3/7/75; Dick Gregory/Rivera, Side 2: William Safire NET TV, 3/6/75; Roundtable, Bella-CIA, Bill Safire on "Today", 2/28/75; CIA Reports (Tape 159)
  - HRH, 3/23-30/75; With Mike Wallace, and "Behind the Lines "on JE HRH, 4/2/75; 2 Sides (Tape 160)
  - Side 1: Theodore White/Tom Snyder, 6/18/75 "Tomorrow "NBC TV 1 a.m., Kevin Phillips-Jeb Magruder a.m. TV, 6/17/75 Side 2: Jack Anderson Interview, a.m. America/ABC TV, 6/18/75 Watergate:, 6/17/75 Henry Kissinger Press Conference PBS:, NET TV (Box 14, Tape 161)
  - Interview with Leon Jaworski, ca. 1976 (Tape 162)
  - Side 1: John Ehrlichman "Today "NBC TV;, 6/6-7/76 "Meet the Press; "Tom Snyder comment on JE/NBC & Simon & Shuster, 5/24/76 Side 2: John Ehrlichman ABC TV, 6/10/76 (Tape 163)
  - John Ehrlichman, Side 1: WMCA radio, 6/8/76; Side 2: WOR TV "Straight Talk", 6/9/76 (Tape 164)
  - John Ehrlichman, Side 1: Pia/NBC TV; Martin Gabel WOR radio, Side 2: Spiro Agnew with Buckley/Merv/Barbara Walters, 6/14/76 (Tape 165)
  - John Ehrlichman: WHBI radio, 6/15/76 (Tape 166)
  - John Ehrlichman, Side 1: "Kup's Show " (pt. 1), 6/27/76; Side 2: "Kup's Show " (pt. 2) Mike Douglas Show, 6/25/76 (Tape 167)
  - Clark Mollenhoff ABC TV, 6/30/76 (Tape 168)
  - JOHN EHRLICHMAN, "a.m. America", 7/6-7/76 (Tape 169)
  - John Ehrlichman: TV news/ABC TV Good Morning America, 7/27/76 (Tape 170)
  - William F. Buckley/Galbraith NBC TV, 7/16/76 (Tape 171)
  - William Safire/WOR radio, 8/30/76 (Tape 172)
  - John Ehrlichman: Phil Donahue Show/WOR TV, 9/2/76 (Tape 173)
  - John Ehrlichman: TV capsules, 9/7-8/76 (Tape 174)
  - Leon Jaworski: CBS FM radio, 2 sides, 10/3/76 (Tape 175)
  - John Dean, 2 sides, 10/13-15/76 (Tape 176)
  - Side 1: John Dean, 10/21/76; WOR TV "Straight Talk", Side 2: Dean/Butterfield, 10/20/76; Jaworski, a.m. TV (Box 15, Tape 177)
  - John Dean (etc.), 2 Sides, 10/24/76 (Tape 178)
  - Side 1: John Dean "Merv", 11/17/76; Side 2: "Tapes", 10/26/76; JOHN EHRLICHMAN, 11/10/76 (Tape 179)
  - Leon Jaworski, Agronsky At Large/NET, David Frost spot, 11/26/76 (Tape 180)
  - Leon Jaworski, "Kup's Show", 12/5/76 (Tape 181)
  - Merv: Dean's/Sahl/Shana, 2 Sides, 1/5/77 (Tape 182)
  - "RICHARD NIXON", An Evening with Clay Felker, 3/5/77 (Tape 183)
  - John Dean, Jeanne Parr/CBS TV, 3/18/77 (Tape 184)
  - Richard Nixon, David Frost (on) Watergate, 2 Sides, 5/4/77 (Tape 185)
  - "RICHARD NIXON" TV Capsules:, 2 Sides, 5/5/77 (Tape 186)
  - "Richard Nixon": TV capsules, 5/6-7/77 (Tape 187)
  - "RICHARD NIXON", Frost Interview #3, (Comments) 2 Sides, 5/19/77 (Tape 188)
  - "RICHARD NIXON" William F. Buckley/, with Reeves-Buchanan, 2 Sides, 5/21/77 (Tape 189)
  - "RICHARD NIXON" 5/25/77; David Frost Interview #4;, 2 Sides, and Jaworski Interview, 5/25/77 (Tape 190)
  - John Mitchell/HRH-Sirica, 2 Sides, 6/3-8/77 (Box 16, Tape 191)